can't do much with it now it's a hard pill to swallow man you wake up is courtney mallory who
is a farmer in colorado who is being terrorized by white people in the town who are trying to
steal his land from him while he's living on the land with his family they just poisoned his cow
that's twelve thousand dollars of meat just gone and they're terrorizing him and their family and
the police are involved and i start to yell because i i want i'm just like why do these people
get to do this why for centuries these people just get to do this over and over and over again i feel
like my soul is the spirit of somebody who keeps coming back just to check on are you still doing
this like why is the universal law why does it allow for this why why did victims of the earthquake
in syria have to wait four days for aid because of politics and government why i hope when i get to
the other side i get to understand why we have to be here with this type of energy and these people
people
you